

CONTACT

- Riyadh , Saudi Arabia
- 00966555088108
- khaled.shoaibi@hotmail.com

SKILLS

- Account management
 Campaign management

- Communications management
 Social media campaign management



Khaled Alshoaibi

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

My goal is to dedicated my scientific and practical knowledge and experience to help the nations orientations and inspiration in order to achieve the kingdoms vision 2030 by creating many initiatives that achieve The Kingdom strategies in various fields, and to help it advance the wheel of development and be an affective member in contributing to the notional advancement to become in the ranks of developed countries.

WORK HISTORY

APCO Worldwide 09/2021 - 01/2022 (Internship Tamheer program) - Riyadh

· Media and Communication specialist

Almethaliah food Company 01/2020 - 12/2020

Branch supervisor - Hofuf

Saudi technology and security comprehensive contro 12/2017 - 02/2018

Data entry - Dammam

01/2017 - 01/2018 Khubeizati bakery

Branch supervisor - Dammam

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Media and Communication, 12/2020 King Faisal University - Saudi Arabia GPA: 4.26

EVENTS AND EXPERIENCES

October 25-28, 2021

(FII EVENT)

Media organizer in The 5th edition of the future investment initiative in Rivadh 2021

(Coordinated Press releases and handled press inquires, manage Media inquires and interview requests, planing and scheduling the announcements, work on the social media platforms Twitter,Instagram during the event) December 24, 2021

Saudi Cup

(Horse racing event)

Communications and public relations organizer

Coordinate with channels and journalists

(Live streaming and interviews schedule)

- . Developing internal and external relationships.
- · Supporting team on projects.
- · Attending external and internal daily zoom meetings.
- · Onsite support responsibilities.
- . Working with a team to create and develop strategies and content for